#### Coordonnées

www.linkedin.com/in/chungnguyen-862148156 (LinkedIn)

Principales compétences

Test Automation
Regression Testing
Mobile Testing

# chung Nguyen

Senior Fullstack Software Tester

Da Nang, Viêt Nam

### Résumé

I am very keen to take on new responsibilities with bigger operations and

high challenges. I am a fast learner and can adapt to new situations so I

don't mind being handed over a hard and pressured job. I am fluent in verbal

and written skills in English and Vietnamese languages. I have been experienced in dealing with different cultures and nationalities. I want to

become a professional QA and maybe a PM in further future.

## Expérience

FPT Software Senior Full stack tester août 2024 - Present (8 mois)

SmartOSC Automation Tester juillet 2022 - juillet 2024 (2 ans 1 mois)

Agillity
Manual Tester
juillet 2021 - juillet 2022 (1 an 1 mois)
Da Nang

Central Viet Nam Realty
Real Estate Agent
janvier 2018 - septembre 2019 (1 an 9 mois)
Vietnam, Da Nang

During my last position, as a real estate agent for CVR, I was responsible for finding clients in many suitable channels to reach the most potential clients for the company. My responsibilities also included helping

Page 1 of 2

clients in searching for their home and take good care of them while they are staying in properties which

were introduced by me. And by this job, I had chances to know about Hoiana and it's environment a lot

## Formation

Da Nang University of Economics
Bachelor's degree, Foreign Trade · (2014 - 2018)